*******roosevelt hote in 2010,
2010年三月的一天  一艘新纽约市公安艇从哈得孙河里
a new york city police boat pulled a 34-year-old white male out of the hudson river: your uncle barney.
捞出了个白种男人 那就是你Barney叔叔
all right,kid,let's hear the story.
好的 孩子 让我们
from the beginning.
从头听起
well,it all started a week ago.
这得从一个星期前说起
i was making time at the local watering hole.
我当时在一个小酒吧里消磨时间
enter.
进来了
a dame.
一位女士
nothing sexier than a man in a fine cravat.
什么都不如一位系着领巾的男士性感
except for a woman who appreciates a fine cravat.
但那还是比不上一个欣赏领巾的女人
how about we just call it a tie?
我们还是叫它领带吧 如何?
you see,a cravat is a kind of tie.
你懂的 领巾就是领带的一种
i get it.
我懂
anyway,next thing you know,i get her back to my place.
不管怎样 后来我把她带回了家
barney.
Barney
when i get in bed with a man,my body becomes a machine fueled by desire,
当我和男人上床时 我的身体里就充斥着欲望
lust and a singular hunger to satisfy my lover's every carnal need.
渴望 强烈的渴望 来满足情人的任何生理需求
good thing the cleaning lady's coming tomorrow.
好消息是明天清洁女工会来打扫
well,good night.
晚安
what?
什么?
wait,what?
等等 什么?
i thought your body was going to become a machine fueled by desire,
我以为你会充斥着欲望
lust and a singular hunger to satisfy my every carnal need.
极度的渴望来满足我任何的生理需求
no.
不
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧  http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com/bbs=-Sync: YTET-sunshine_zp
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 尘沙 wyy 校对: 葱家的小毛毛 时间轴: YTET-sunshine_zp
How i met your mother Season five Episode seventeen
老爸老妈浪漫史 第五季 第十七集
you know,i really think that don and i are hitting our stride as a news team.
我真的觉得Don和我作为搭档 关系有了很大的进展
well,all credit goes to this lady on my left.
一切都归功于我左边的这位女士
oh,come on.
哦 拜托
that story you did on which rodents to avoid on the subway.
你讲那个故事 试图让人再不敢带啮齿动物上地铁
the answer may surprise you.
结果能让你们大吃一惊哦
it's all of them.
是所有的都没了
well,i got to run,okay?
我得走了 行吗?
- i'll see you. - it's good to meet you.
- 再见 - 很高兴见到你们
- okay - yeah,you,too.
- 好的 - 是 我也是
bye,don.
拜拜 Don
okay,robin,that guy is awesome.
好吧 Robin 那人太棒了
he's funny,he's smart,he's handsome.
他又风趣 又聪明 又帅
you got to scoop him up before someone else does.
你得比别人先抢到他
i hope you're not talking about you.
我希望你不是在说你自己
it has been four months since you broke up with barney.
你和Barney分手已经有4个月了
maybe it's time to put yourself back out there.
也许该是时候放手了
yeah,exactly.
对 没错
barney's dating again,and he couldn't be happier.
Barney又开始约会了 他实在是太爽了
i couldn't be more unhappy.
实在是太不爽了
all night long,she's hot and heavy for me.
整个晚上 她都很性感 很风骚
i get her back to my place,and she just bolts?
我把她带回家 然后她就甩手走了?
i mean,at least when i run out on a girl,
至少当我要抛弃女孩的时候
i have the common courtesy to sleep with her first.
我也会先和她睡上一觉 这是基本的
it's.it's called manners.
这 这叫礼貌
sounds like she read that book,of course you're still single-- take a look at yourself,you dumb slut.
听上去她好像读过那本书  《你当然还是单身--瞧瞧你自己 你个蠢货》
what?it.it's this book that helps single girls find a husband.
怎么了? 它 它是本帮单身女孩们 寻找自己的另一半的书
it's robin's copy.
这是Robin的书
i've just.i leafed through it a little bit.
我只是 我只是翻看了一下
really.
真的吗
- were you getting a mani-pedi? - okay,okay,okay.
- 你索性去做个指甲护理算了? (讽刺Ted像女人)  - 好 好 好
fine.
好
barney,when you were with this girl,did she subtly slip the word "sex" into conversation?
Barney 当你和这女孩在一起的时候 她有没有很巧妙地说出"性"这个字?
i'm in the inter-sex-tion,and i only have a couple of sex before the light changes.
在变绿灯之前我和别人在做爱
i mean,everyone's honking at me,and it totally sex,
每个人都对着我按喇叭 那真是 讨厌
but i can't turn around because a jogger slipped and fell in horse sex-crement.
但我没法转身 因为一个在慢跑的人 滑倒了 栽在了一坨马粪上 (话中真是充斥着Sex)
go on.
继续
继续说下去
did she make excuses to establish physical contact with you?
她有没有借机和你有肢体接触?
is this cashmere?
这是山羊绒的吗?
cashmere?
山羊绒?
this is hand-spun virgin merino.
这是手纺的纯美利奴羊毛
the fibers in this suit are less than 12 microns thick.
这件西服上的每根纤维都不到12微米
12 microns.
12微米
i love a tiny fiber.
我喜欢细纤维
well,you're in luck,because mine's the tiniest.
那你走运了 因为我的是最细的
and the more you touch it,the softer it gets.
你摸得越多 它就越软
she did that,too.
她也那么做了
now,here is the final test.
现在来看最后一个测试
next time you see her,ask her out for the following night.
你下次见到她的时候 约她第二天晚上出来
the book says that's forbidden,so she'll probably give you some lame excuse like this:
这书上说那是不可以的 所以她很可能会给你些糟糕的借口 比如:
"ooh,i can't do anything tomorrow night.
"哦 明晚我没时间
i've already made plans to clean my garbage disposal and treat myself to a bubble bath.
我要清理我的垃圾处理机 然后再洗个泡泡澡
but how about next week sometime?
下周怎么样?
you're trying that of course you're still single-- take a look at yourself,you dumb slut crap on me.
你在用《你当然还是单身-- 瞧瞧你自己 你个蠢货》上面的废话来应付我
it's not crap.
那不是废话
of course you're still single-- take a look at yourself,you dumb slut is a brilliant book.
《你当然还是单身--瞧瞧你自己 你个蠢货》 是本很棒的书
and.
而且
it scares away guys who are only interested in getting laid.
它能吓走那些只想着上床的人
why not just say you have a kid?
那为什么不直接说你有个孩子?
you'd be surprised how many jerks there are out there.
你可能没法预料外面有多少混蛋
that's why the book says never sleep with a guy on the first date.
所以这本书才说永远不要 在第一次约会就和男人上床
totally.
完全同意
or the second date.
第二次也不要
of course.
当然
or the third date.
第三次也是
well.
好的
or the fourth date.
还有第四次
well,just tell me how many dates!
你就告诉我要等多少次吧!
seventeen.s.s.
17次
excuse me,is anyone using this?
抱歉 这里有人吗?
yep,here it is: no sex until after 17 dates.
是 这里写着: 17次约会前不要和人上床
lily: barney,if you're not going to take her out on 17 dates,i think you should just give it up.
Barney 如果你不能等到第17次的话 我想你还是放弃吧
oh,no.
哦 不
i'm not the one who's going to give it up.
我才不会放弃
she is.
放弃的人是她
because,thanks to ted's book.
因为 多亏了Ted的书
that's robin's.it's robin's.
那是Robin的 是Robin的
i can stay two steps ahead of her at all times.
我总能比她抢先两步
there's a loophole in here somewhere,and i'm going to find it.
这里面肯定会有漏洞 我要把它找出来
hello.
喂
hey,robin.
嘿 Robin
oh,hey,don.
哦 嘿 Don
listen,uh.
听着 呃
do you want to go out saturday night?
你星期六晚上愿不愿意出来?
saturday night.
星期六晚上
is he asking you out?
他是不是在约你出去?
say yes!
答应他! 答应他!
look,don,um.
呃 Don 呃
listen,it.
听着 你
it's really sweet of you to ask,and you're a great guy.
你能约我真的很好 你真的是个好人
yes,i will go out with you.
是的 我会跟你出去的
robin,are you okay?
Robin 你没事吧?
um,i just had a little cold.
我只是有点感冒
that's probably what you're hearing.
所以你那听起来声音可能有点怪
but saturday night sounds great.
但星期六晚上不错
we can even go to a steak house,and you can bring home some prime rib for my friend,marshall.
我们甚至可以去一家牛排馆 你可以带些烧烤牛排给我的朋友 Marshall
okay,gotta go.love you.bye
好了 我得走了 爱你 拜拜
what the hell are you thinking?
你到底在想什么?
robin,you've got to do this,okay?
Robin 你必须得去 知道吗?
a great guy like don is rare.
像Don这么好的人不多啊
and speaking of rare,prime rib-- don't forget.
对了 说到稀有 烧烤牛排 别忘了哦
thank you.
谢谢
oh,my god.
哦 天哪
i don't believe it.
真不敢相信
guys.
伙计们
this is her!
这是她的照片!
she wrote the book.
这本书是她写的
her name must be anita.
她一定是叫Anita
okay.
好的
my plan was to sleep with her,but this changes everything.
我本来计划的是要和她上床 现在计划有变了
new plan: i'm going to sleep with her.
新计划是: 我一定要和她上床
boy,this girl that barney's going after,she kind of sounds like the anti-barney.
伙计们 这个Barney正在追的女孩 听上去好像很讨厌Barney
i love how the universe decided to bring those two together.
我真高兴看到上帝让这两个人相遇了
actually,anita's going after barney because i told her to.
事实上 是我叫Anita去追Barney的
??wait,you sicced anita on barney?
等等 你让Anita去整Barney?
how do you even know her?
你怎么会认识她的?
she was on my show.
她上过我的节目
but,um,if you had to summarize your book in 30 words or less.
嗯 如果让你用30个甚至更少的词 来概括你的书话
i'll summarize it in one word,robin.
我会用一个词来概括她 Robin
and that word is "no.
那个词就是 "不"
" by saying no constantly and consistently,you empower yourself
一直坚持说不的话 你就会更强大
while simultaneously turning any jerk into a submissive,sniveling,puddle of a man.
同时也能让那些混蛋 变得顺从 对着你痛哭流涕
and isn't that every girl's dream?
这难道不是每个女孩的梦想吗?
after the break,we're going to talk about your new book,
广告之后  我们会继续讨论你的新书
of course you don't have a retirement plan yet--
你当然还没有一个退休计划--
take a look at yourself,you dumb slut,due out in june.
瞧瞧你自己 你个混蛋 7月发售
we'll be right back.
我们马上回来
we're clear.
好了
you guys want any coffee?
你们要不要喝咖啡?
oh,you know what,mike,that'd be great.
哦 Mike 那太好了
you?
你呢?
no.
不用
what about you,robin?you dating anyone?
你呢 Robin? 你在和别人交往吗?
dating's not really my bag right now.
我现在真的没有约会的心情
did somebody break your heart?
是不是有人伤了你的心?
and then,i-i told her everything.
之后 我就把所有的事都告诉她了
it just came pouring out.
就那么全说出来了
and by the end of it,she said.
最后 她说
this barney needs to be taught a lesson.
这个Barney应该受点教训
you say the word,and i will destroy him.
只要你同意 我就会毁了他
what do you mean?
什么意思?
i can use the power of "no" to break your friend,barney.
我可以用"不"的力量来打击你的朋友Barney
just say the word.
只要你点头
come on,that-that stuff doesn't really work,does it?
拜托 那其实起不了什么作用 对吗?
i didn't know what you wanted,so i got you a cappuccino,an espresso,a latte,a decaf.
我不知道你想喝什么 所以我给你拿了 卡布奇诺 意大利浓咖啡 拿铁 脱因咖啡
oh,hi,robin.
哦 嗨 Robin
and this is a turkish coffee.
这是土耳其咖啡
thank you,mike.
谢谢你 Mike
think about it.
考虑一下吧
robin: i didn't think i was going to think about it,but then.
我以为我不会动心的 但是之后
i thought about it.
我考虑了一下
oh,this pilates instructor was off the charts.
哦 这个普拉提教练简直太正了
picture robin,but younger.
长得像Robin一样 但比她年轻点
and bigger boobs.
胸也比她大点
maybe not bigger,but more shapely.
也许差不多大 但更有型
and bigger.
而是大一点
hello?
喂?
- i get her up against the stairmaster,and we. - do it.
- 我把她带到登山跑步机后面 然后我们 - 做了
spoilers.
别抢我的话
- anyway,we do it. - it's done.
- 不管怎样 我们做爱了 - 没问题
thank you,mike.
谢谢你 Mike
i know,it was stupid,but you have to understand,back then,
我知道我很蠢 但你得知道 那时候
i was still really upset about the breakup.
我对分手的事还是很伤心
i was going though my mourning period.
我还在悲伤期
there was a lot of scotch and a lot of long nights at the shooting range.
我心里有很多伤痕 有很多个长夜我都是在射击场度过的
i hope those weren't the same nights.
我希望那不是那些晚上
geez,lily.
上帝啊 Lily
it's not like i remember all of them.
我也不想记起它们
hey,babe.
嘿 宝贝
did you know that robin was going through a mourning period?
你知道Robin有那么一段 很伤心的时间吗?
i mean,she seemed fine after the breakup.
分手后 她看上去还好啊
oh,you know how she is.
你知道她就是这样的人
she tries to keep her emotions to herself.
她想把自己的情绪隐藏起来
but yeah,i caught her crying a couple times.
但我好几次撞见她偷偷哭
she cried?
她会哭?
like,real tears?
掉眼泪真哭?
but that means.
可那意味着...
oh,no.
哦 不
and then,marshall realized what a jackass he had been to robin.
于是Marshall意识到他对待Robin 有多混球
exactly.
就是
barney's dating again,and he couldn't be happier.
Barney重回约会战场 快活无比
i mean,that guy has been active.
我是说 那家伙可活跃了
sexually.
随性所欲
i mean,he's just been,like,bang,bang,bang!
我说 他光顾着啪啪啪了
you know?
你明白吗?
it's like.
就像是
bang,bang,bang,bang,bang,bang!
啪啪啪 啪啪啪!
?bang,bang,bang,bangity bang ??i said a-bang,bang,bangity bang ??bang,bang,bang ?
啪里啪啪啪 啪里啪啪
?bang,bang,bangity bang ??i said a-bang,bang,bangity bang.
啪里啪噗啪啪 噗里啪啪啪啪
how could you let me do that?
你怎么能由着我那样?
you're my wife,you're supposed to stop me from embarrassing myself in public.
你是我老婆  你应该阻止我在公共场合出丑
i know,but that song's kind of catchy.
我知道 但那歌真朗朗上口
bang,bang,bangity bang ??bang,bang,bangity bang ?
啪里啪啪啪 啪里啪啪
?i said bang,bang,bangity bang ??a-bang,bang,bangity bang.
啪里啪噗啪啪 噗里啪啪啪啪
damn it.
该死
i've read that thing cover to cover,and i can't find a loophole.
我把那东西从头读到尾巴 一个破绽也没找着
what am i going to do?
我该怎么办
well,there is one other option,but,uh,nah,you're not ready.
还有一个办法 但是你没准备好
tell me.
告诉我
well,if you have to seal the deal in just one date,it's got to be one doozy of a date,right?
要是你想第一次约会就上垒 那约会可得不同凡响
i'm not talking dinner and a movie.
我说的不是晚餐加电影
i'm not talking mini-golf.
不是迷你高尔夫
i'm talking.
我是说
17 dates worth of romance wrapped up into one incredible night.
17次约会的浪漫 浓缩在一次无与伦比的约会里
i'm talking about.
我是说
a superdate.
超级约会
a superdate?
超级约会?
that sounds kind of lame.
听着有点废
what if we call it a megadate?
不如叫无敌约会?
- if you want my help,it's a superdate. - all right.
- 如果你要我帮忙 就得叫超级约会 - 好吧
leave it to me.
看我的
i'll plan the whole thing.
我会做好全盘计划
you're going to plan the whole thing?
你来做全盘计划?
i bet it'll be all gooey and romantic,huh?
我猜会很小资情调的浪漫哈
gooey and romantic?
很小资情调的浪漫?
小资情调?
barney.
Barney
?you don't have to take her ?
你不用带她
?to paris or peru ?
去巴黎或秘鲁
uh,ted,what are you doing?
Ted 你在做啥?
?you just have to make her understand ?
你只要让她明白
ted,people are looking at us.
Ted 别人看着我们呢
?what she means to you ?
她对你有多重要
oh,god,really?
你来真的
you're really going to do this right now?
你现在就来?
?on your superdate ?
当你享受超级约会
?troubles of the world will simply have to wait ?
世上一切烦忧消失无影无踪
?for wonders and amazement ??served upon a silver plate ?
奇迹美梦争相成真
?hurry up now,don't be late ?
快来吧 别迟到
?'cause hand in hand you'll find a land ?
手牵手 踏上新大陆
?where paradise awaits ?
天堂近在咫尺
and then boom!
然后"砰!"
fireworks over the manhattan skyline!
焰火点燃曼哈顿夜空!
you kiss her.
你吻她
and that's your superdate.
这就是你的超级约会
that sounds gooey and romantic.
真是小资情调的浪漫啊
- strip club? - strip club.
- 去脱衣舞酒吧? - 脱衣舞酒吧
finally,the night of the big dates arrived.
终于盛大约会的日子来了
so,tonight's the big night.
今晚是大日子哈
where's the d-bag taking you?
Don傻帽准备带你去哪儿?
that's not a good nickname for don.
这个绰号叫Don不好
i'll think of a better one.
我想个好点的
you know,that,i just.i canceled.
我取消了
what do you mean you.wait.
什么意思 等一下
what's wrong?
怎么了?
robin canceled her date.
Robin取消了她的约会
what?
什么?
like an hour ago
一个小时前她还兴高采烈想着去呢
robin scherbatsky.
Robin Scherbatsky
you look like the classiest,most expensive prostitute ever.
你看着就像史上最高贵最昂贵的妓女
oh,thank you.
哦 谢谢
*****
要跟Don约会你期待吗?
you know what?
你知道吗
i kinda am.
我还真有点
dot tell marshall.
别告诉Marshall
i won't.
我不告诉他
i bet you'll have a nice time tonight.
我猜你今晚会过得很愉快
not,however,a super time.
然而不是极致愉快
a super time will be had by bary on his date with anita.
极致愉快的体验将发生在 Barney和Anita今晚的约会
yep.
嗯
carriage ride,dinner at le tombeur des culottes.
马车兜风 烛光晚餐
they're calling it a superde,so.
他们管这叫做超级约会
ted!
Ted!
how could you do that?
你怎么能那么干?
robin ju got over her mourning period!
Robin才刚刚走出情伤!
she seemed so happy after the breakup.
她分手之后看上去很快活
ohted.
哦 Ted
so unobserva.such a guy.
真不会察言观色 大老粗
she was obviously crushed.
她明显快崩溃了
wait,but that would mean.
等下 那就是说
oh,no.
哦 不
and then i reazed what a jackass i'd been to robin.
于是我意识到我对Robin有多混球
- i said a-bang,bang,bangity bang ? - hey,whatcha singing?
- 啪里啪啪啪 啪里啪啪 - 嗨 你唱啥呢?
******
我在唱Barney的风流艳史呢
cot me in for a verse.
下一段算上我
great.
好极了
?bang,bang,bangity bang ??i said a-bang,bang,ngity bang ??bang,bg,bang ?
啪里啪啪啪 啪里啪啪
?bang,bang,bgity bang ??i said a-bang,bang.
啪里啪噗啪啪 噗里啪啪啪啪
?no!
不!
oh,god.
老天
where is she?
她在哪?
i think she's in the restroom.
我想她在洗手间
no,guys,guys,i'm fine,i'm fine.
伙计们 我没事 我没事
why would you do that?
你干嘛?
because i'm angry at you.
因为我生你的气
i'm angry at me.
我生自己的气
i'm angry at ted.
我生Ted的气
and frankly,i'm still angry at the empire.
老实说 我现在还为帝国气愤呢 (星球大战里的帝国)
why are u angry at me?
你为啥生我的气?
de,you've been a real jerk in front of robin while she's been gng through her mourning period.
你对Robin差劲透了 她还在经历情伤呢
mourning period?
情伤?
she hasn't been going through anmourning period.
她没有情伤什么的
sonobservant.
真不会察言观色
such a guy.
大老粗
h,barney,sit down,you need to hear some stuff.
Barney 坐好 有些事你得听听
what-what,is she set or something?
啥 她是难过还是怎么的?
of course she's upset.
她当然难过
take a look at yourself,you dumb slut.
看看你自己 你个淫荡的蠢货
and then aunt lily told barney every excruciating detail of what he hadn't been seeing since the breakup.
然后Lily阿姨巨细无遗地告诉他 分手以来他没看见的所有伤人细节
you should've seen this girl.
你得见见这姑娘
bang,ping,pa-dow,ga-donk.
乒 乓 啪嗒 嘎咚
okay,i'm leaving.
好了 我走了
so.
然后
we get up to my place.
我们回到我家
bang,bangity bang,bang,bang,bang ??i said a-bang,bang,bangity bang ??bang,bang,bang.
啪里啪啪啪 啪里啪啪 啪里啪噗啪啪 噗里啪啪啪啪
i can't believe robin's been so upset.
我不敢相信Robin那么难过
i can't beeve you threw up in your stormtrooper helmet.
我不敢相信你吐在你的风暴兵头盔里
i disomething worse in it after the phantom mena premiere.
我在"幽灵的威胁"首映礼后干过更糟的事 (即星球大战前传一)
so,she's been this way ever since we broke up?
我们分手以后她一直这样?
actually,she was doing mu better until you decided to gon this stupid superdate with anita.
实际上 她已经好多了 直到你决定要跟Anita来场愚蠢的超级约会
and now she's off sulking god knows where.
现在天知道她上哪儿郁闷去了
i know where.
我知道在哪
hey.
嗨
barney,what's up?
Barney 怎么了?
thought you were,um,going on some big date.
我以为你要去浪漫约会
robin,i know you're upset.
Robin 我知道你很难过
what?
啥?
no.
没有
i-i-i have.i've nevereen happier.
我我我再高兴不过了
and-and th anita sounds lovely.
Anita听上去好可爱
i am so glad that you two just.
我真替你们俩高兴
randomly happened to find each other.
就这么随随便便找到了对方
it just warms my frickin' heart.
我TM心里感到一阵温暖
so,you re you're not upset?
这么说你不难过?
of course i'm upset,barney.
我当然难过 Barney
don't you see how consntly talking about your conquests makes me feel like i'm just another numb to you?
你看不出来你老在谈你那些战绩 让我觉得我只是给你的艳遇添上一笔
but you're not just anothenumber to me.
可你不仅仅是我战绩上一笔
you know,and-and now you're taking anita,who you bare know,
你现在要带上Anita 你都不怎么认识她
on this amazing date,en i never got treated that way it just.
来场绝妙的约会 我从来没享受过这种待遇
it just sucks,that's all.it just suck  wow.
糟透了 就这样 糟透了
i knew i was bad at being a boyfriend,but i had nodea i'd be so much worse at beingn ex-boyfriend.
我知道我当男友糟透了 但我一点 都不知道我当前男友更糟糕
i'm sorry.
我很抱歉
what can i do to make it up to you?
我怎么做才能补偿你?
nothing,barney.
什么都不能 Barney
you've-you've already proven that i'm n important to you.
你已经行动证明了我对你毫不重要
stop that,i'm serious.
别说了 我是认真的
ask me f anything.
要我做什么都可以
uh,okay.
呃 好吧
don't sleep with anita.
不要和Anita上床
done.
遵命
barney,of coue you're going to sleep with her.
Barney 你肯定要和她上床
why else would you be taking her on this surdate?
否则你带她赴这场超级约会是为什么?
she's not going on the superdate,robin.
超级约会她去不成了 Robin
you are.
换你去
your uncle barney finally gave aunt robin th superdate she truly deserved.
你们的Barney叔叔最终给了Robin阿姨 她值得拥有的超级约会
with a guy sheruly deserved.
和她真正值得拥有的男人
ofourse,there was still one loose end.
当然 还有一件事悬而未决
barney.
Barney
oh,he anita.
嗨 Anita
i-totally meant to call you.
我正想打电话给你
well,i'm-i'm breaking all my rules coming down here,but nobody standme up like that.
我打破所有规则来这里 没有人这样放过我鸽子
so,are we going out or what?
我们还要不要约会?
i'sorry.i....
抱歉
i made a promise to a friend.
我答应了一个朋友
i have to sano.
我不得不拒绝你
oh.
哦
oh,i see.
我明白了
ho you're trying the "no" thing on me.
你给我来欲拒还迎这套
you really think that's going to work?
你真以为能管用?
'cause it won't.
才不管用
okay,how about this.i'll cut you a deal.
好吧 不如这样 我放你一马
maybe.
也许
you might get lucky after the 12th date.
第12次约会上你就能一亲芳泽
no.
不
-  th11th date. - no
-  第11次 - 不
- fifth date. - no
- 第5次 - 不
- tonight. - no
- 就今晚 - 不
- tonight before dinner. - no
- 今晚晚餐前 - 不
- how about you?you interested  - yeah.
- 你呢? 感兴趣吗?  - 当然
come on,barney.
来嘛 Barney
i'm sorry,anita.
我很抱歉 Anita
the answer is no.
我的答案还是不
we,good.
很好
because my answer is no,too.
因为我的答案也是不
okay,here's my final offer.
好啦 最后一次机会
barney!
Barney!
and that's my story.
这就是我的故事
well,here's a $500 ticket for jumpg in the river.
这是跳河的500刀罚单
i hope it was worth it.
我希望这一切值得
i hope so,too.
我也这么希望
?dah-de-dah-de-dah ?it's an d wives' tale.
这是个老太太的笑话
oh,hey,robin.
嗨 Robin
how did the big date go?
约会咋样了?
uh,pretty well.
挺好的
pretty,uh,pretty well.
挺好的 很不错
like ho"pretty well"?
怎么个"挺好的"法?
oh,guys,guys,come on.
伙计们 拜托
it was fine.
还不错啦
you know,it was nice.
你明白 还不错
we had a good time.
我们过得很愉快
let's just,uh.
我们 嗯
let's just lve it at that,okay.
就说到这儿吧 好吗
although,um,********?
然而 的确有这么件有意思的事?
i said a-bang,bang,bangity bang ??i said a-bang,bang,??a-bang,bang,bang,bang,bang,bangitbang ?
啪里啪啪 啪里啪啪啪
?i said a-bang,bang,ang,?bangity bang ?
啪里啪噗啪啪 噗里啪啪啪啪